Hong Il-tak said…
he wants to sleep
in the same room
What the hell?
Why is this jerk
acting like this?
Guess you have
no choice
since Il-tak wants
to sleep with me
That's bull****
Who said I want
to sleep with you?
Hey, Hong Il-tak
Are you really
going to sleep with him?
No, I want
to sleep with you…
What the hell
is wrong with him?
They're going
to fight again
We'll all get kicked off
the field trip
Wait, guys
Why don't the three of us
stay here?
Let's be friendly
How about it?
But seriously, why does
Hyeon-wu want
to share a room?
I mean
this works out for me
Whatever it is
this is my chance
I'm going to
become his friend
I should
change clothes first
What the f***?
The last person
to touch my bag was…
Il-tak
Yeah?
Did you pack
all your stuff?
Yeah
You forgot
your toothbrush
I'll put it in
Sure, thanks
Yep
Don't touch
anything inside!
Of course I won't
Hong Yi-yeon
you crazy bitch
Why is this here?
Is it my parent's?
Hey, Hong Il-tak!
Are you here?